[
  [
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Champions Trophy 2013?",
      "answers": [
        "Pakistan",
        "Australia",
        "India",
        "New Zealand"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "India"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC T20 World Cup 2016?",
      "answers": [
        "West Indies",
        "England",
        "Inida",
        "Australia"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "West Indies"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Cricket World Cup 2019?",
      "answers": [
        "Australia",
        "England",
        "India",
        "West Indies"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "England"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Champions Trophy 2009?",
      "answers": [
        "India",
        "Pakistan",
        "England",
        "Australia"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Australia"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC T20 World Cup 2007?",
      "answers": [
        "Pakistan",
        "India",
        "England",
        "West Indies"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "India"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Cricket World Cup 1975?",
      "answers": [
        "Sri Lanka",
        "West Indies",
        "India",
        "Pakistan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "West Indies"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Champions Trophy 2017?",
      "answers": [
        "West Indies",
        "Australia",
        "Inida",
        "Pakistan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Pakistan"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC T20 World Cup 2010?",
      "answers": [
        "England",
        "Australia",
        "Sri Lanka",
        "Pakistan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "England"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Cricket World Cup 1979?",
      "answers": [
        "England",
        "West Indies",
        "India",
        "Pakistan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "West Indies"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Champions Trophy 2006?",
      "answers": [
        "England",
        "India",
        "Australia",
        "Pakistan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Australia"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC T20 World Cup 2024?",
      "answers": [
        "Pakistan",
        "England",
        "Australia",
        "India"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "India"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Cricket World Cup 1987?",
      "answers": [
        "Australia",
        "West Indies",
        "Pakistan",
        "India"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Australia"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Champions Trophy 2004?",
      "answers": [
        "England",
        "West Indies",
        "Australia",
        "India"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "West Indies"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC T20 World Cup 2009?",
      "answers": [
        "India",
        "Australia",
        "West Indies",
        "Pakistan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Pakistan"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Cricket World Cup 1996?",
      "answers": [
        "Sri Lanka",
        "Australia",
        "India",
        "England"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Sri Lanka"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which player has the most runs in One Day Internationals?",
      "answers": [
        "Rahul Dravid",
        "Sachin Tendulkar",
        "Muhammad Yousuf",
        "Rickey Ponting"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Sachin Tendulkar"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC T20 World Cup 2012?",
      "answers": [
        "India",
        "England",
        "West Indies",
        "Sri Lanka"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "West Indies"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Cricket World Cup 1983?",
      "answers": [
        "Pakistan",
        "England",
        "West Indies",
        "India"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "India"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which player has the most runs in Tests?",
      "answers": [
        "Joe Root",
        "Rahul Dravid",
        "Sachin Tendulkar",
        "Rickey Ponting"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Sachin Tendulkar"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC T20 World Cup 2021?",
      "answers": [
        "Sri Lanka",
        "Pakistan",
        "England",
        "Australia"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Australia"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Cricket World Cup 1992?",
      "answers": [
        "India",
        "West Indies",
        "Pakistan",
        "England"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Pakistan"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the IPL in 2010?",
      "answers": [
        "Kolkata Knight Riders",
        "Mumbai Indias",
        "Deccan Chargers",
        "Chennai Super Kings"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Chennai Super Kings"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the PSL in 2016?",
      "answers": [
        "Islamabad United",
        "Karachi Kings",
        "Quetta Gladiators",
        "Lahore Qalandars"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Islamabad United"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Cricket World Cup 1999?",
      "answers": [
        "Australia",
        "India",
        "West Indies",
        "Pakistan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Australia"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the IPL in 2012?",
      "answers": [
        "Mumbai Indias",
        "Chennai Super Kings",
        "Kolkata Knight Riders",
        "Deccan Chargers"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Kolkata Knight Riders"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the PSL in 2019?",
      "answers": [
        "Karachi Kings",
        "Quetta Gladiators",
        "Islamabad United",
        "Lahore Qalandars"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Quetta Gladiators"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Cricket World Cup 2011?",
      "answers": [
        "England",
        "India",
        "Sri Lanka",
        "Australia"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "India"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the IPL in 2016?",
      "answers": [
        "Mumbai Indias",
        "Chennai Super Kings",
        "Kolkata Knight Riders",
        "Sunrisers Hyderabad"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Sunrisers Hyderabad"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the PSL in 2023?",
      "answers": [
        "Quetta Gladiators",
        "Lahore Qalandars",
        "Karachi Kings",
        "Islamabad United"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Lahore Qalandars"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the ICC Cricket World Cup 2003?",
      "answers": [
        "England",
        "Pakistan",
        "Australia",
        "West Indies"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Australia"
    }
  ]
]